sweetcidermusic.com 2013-03-10

# Sweet Cider Music - Privacy Policy

**Sweet Cider Music - PRIVACY POLICY**

**Privacy Statement of Sweet Cider Music**

We are committed to protecting your privacy. The privacy, confidence, and trust of individuals who visit our website is important to us. No personal information is collected at this site unless provided voluntarily by an individual while participating in an activity that asks for the information.

**Cookies** "Cookies" are small piece of data that is sent to your Internet browser from a Web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. A cookie can't read data off of your computer hard disk or read cookie files created by other websites. Cookies do not damage your system. They are used to keep track of and store information so the user does not have to supply the information multiple times. The information that is collected through cookies at this site is handled in the same manner as other information collected here. You can configure your web browser to refuse cookies or to notify you when a web site attempts to send you a cookie. You can also check your hard drive for cookie files and delete them from your computer.

**Links to Other Sites** This website contains links to many other websites. These include links to websites operated by other government agencies, nonprofit organizations, and private businesses. We are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of these sites and suggest you review their privacy statements.

**NOTIFICATION and CHANGES** Any modifications to our privacy practices will be reflected here. If we change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on this page so our users are aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under which circumstances, if any, we disclose it. Users should check this policy frequently to keep abreast of any changes. 

Permissions to Link or Post Permission is granted for linking to our site, individual pages or articles within the site.

Copyright © 2009 Sweet Cider Music. All rights reserved.

The template is being taken from www.freewebsitetemplates.com as per free download and is used for informational purposes.

[ **Video Production Companies**](http://www.beholderproductions.com/):Beholder Production is a video production company. Some of the excellent video services that it offers are script writing and story boards, HD video production and video editing and post production.
